Okay. So, what we're going to do um is
we're going to install GitHub Desktop.
GitHub Desktop makes a lot of Git
commands easier because you don't have
to memorize how to interact with it in
the terminal. You can exclusively
interact with Git from the terminal. Um
but it can be complicated if it's your
first time. So, what we're going to do
is we're going to use GitHub Desktop,
which gives us a graphic user interface,
something we can click on, and it walks
us through a very similar flow to the
commands. so that when you h do learn
the commands um you're already familiar
with the flow of how GitHub works or
sorry how git works. So what you're
going to do is you're going to search
GitHub desktop and then you're going to
click download GitHub desktop. It should
automatically detect what um what
operating system you're running. In my
case, it detected that I have an Apple
Silicon um Mac. So I'm going to download
and it's going to go to my downloads
folder.
And as soon as it's done, um, you can
see it popped up here in downloads. I'm
going to click on it. And it has put the
desktop application in my downloads
folder. I'm going to drag it.
I'm going to open it up.
And it says, are you sure you want to
open it? I am sure I want to open it.
And now it says I can sign in to
github.com.
And I'm going to end this video here um
because the signin process is the same
for both a Windows and a Mac. And I'm
going to show the signin process in the
next